A warm house to protect me
from the wind and rain.
And they gave me some fluffy warm bedding.
Kompeito in the bottle.
So what more can I ask for?
I hope you're not completely
satisfied with one or two!
At this rate, it's going to take you a
hundred years to fill the bottle.
It's okay, Ioryogi-san!
Even if it takes a hundred years,
Kobato is ready!
Are you telling me to hang out with
you for one hundred years?!
Kobato.
Dou sureba iin dakke?
Atarimae no kototte itsumo
Muzukashii na
Ureshii toki waratte
Suki na toki ni utaitai dake
Na no ni
Itsuka negai wa kanau to
Demo "itsuka" tte dore kurai?
Machikirenai yo
123! no aizu de ryoute hirogete
Zenshin ni hikari wo atsumete
Doko ni aru no?
Oshiete, watashi ni dekiru koto
Meippai kizu tsuite
Seiippai hashitte
Nan juu kai koronde naite
Sore de mo mada
Akireru kurai
Ashita wo shinjiteru
...Spring Green and the Flutter of the Heart.
You know what you have to do.
Yes sir. I will heal broken hearts
and collect more kompeito.
Little birds are singing.
Flowers are sparkling in the morning dew.
They smell great!
Just wake up a little earlier in the morning,
and there are all these discoveries.
Aren't you getting a little carried away
with this little walk you're having?
It's not like that!
Look! What a pretty little street!
She's beautiful...
Um, excuse me...
I didn't think anyone was watching.
Why are you crying?
I wonder...
Huh?
Because the fresh leaves
are so pretty, perhaps?
Do pretty fresh leaves make you cry?
That's a hard one to understand.
Sorry.
By the way...
Do I know you?
My name is Kobato Hanato.
I'm Kohaku.
Kohaku?
Ioryogi-san! You're a
stuffed toy, remember?
Are you the Kohaku from Tenkai?
Tenkai?
Yes.
That's why you don't seem quite human.
Who is this?
It's Ioryogi-san.
It's all right with her.
Is that true?
Ioryogi-san... I've heard that name before.
Ummmm...
Hmmmm...
I forget.
Come on, don't you remember a guy with
a name that sounds like Ioryogi?!
That sounds like Ioryogi?
Would you happen to be the "Iorogi-san"?
Yeah, you got it.
What? You two know each other?
Not much more than each other's name.
I never would've imagined
Iorogi-san to be so cute.
Well, as for this appearance...
People know me as Ioryogi here.
I understand, "Ioryogi-san".
And you're Kobato?
Yes!
I'd better water the plants in the
yard before the sun gets too strong.
So long!
Yes!
What are you doing?
Oh, you scared me.
I was looking at the leaves.
No matter how much I look at them,
they don't make me cry.
I wonder why.
Beats me. When I look at these
leaves, my eyes water.
Really? Your eyes water?
Could you tell me why that happens?
This person supposedly here to help is so lazy.
So my eyes water just thinking that it's going
to take all day gathering these leaves.
I'll do it!
I'll be finished in no time!
What a klutz. Here, let me help you.
Kobato!
I'll help, too!
Thank you all!
What are you doing?
I'm trying to understand the
reason behind Kohaku's tears.
If she's hurt, I'd like to offer some healing.
I don't know how much good looking
at that is going to do to help you.
But it might give me some sort of hint!
I wasn't able to figure it out.
I'm not surprised.
Well then, I'll just have to get up early
tomorrow and go ask her again.
I overslept!
I knew this would happen.
She's not here.
Welcome home.
It must have been a long night.
It's Kohaku!
Wait!
Why?
Don't be a nuisance.
Nuisance?
If you go out there right now,
you'll just be in their way!
There was no need to come
out to greet me, Dear.
You should have just waited for me at home.
I enjoy walking home with
you like this, Shuichiro.
Besides, I want to spend every
minute I can by your side.
My, my, what a lovely couple.
It's a gorgeous mansion.
Totally out of your league.
Actually, you have no business here.
I don't believe that. Even rich people
get their hearts broken.
Where did you learn that?
I studied the convenience store magazines!
Ioryogi-san?
Huh?
When would be a good time to approach her?
Uh no, you're not getting the point.
Sorry I can't keep my promise today.
That's all right. You were up all night.
Besides, your patients matter more.
You matter just as much.
Kobato, like I said, there's no place
for you here. Let's go.
Wha- Hey! No!
Dear spirits in the water.
Heed to my calling.
Lend your strength to enrich the trees.
Come together to save their lives.
Bring on the blessed rains. Pour!
It's beautiful.
Kobato?!
Ioryogi-san?
I'm soaking wet, you idiot!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm really truly sorry.
No, we shouldn't have been
trespassing. I'm sorry.
How did you find this place?
Well actually...
I saw you walking with a man yesterday, and...
Huh?
Sorry, I followed you!
But I needed to find out why you were crying.
I just couldn't understand.
I mean, it has been on my mind and...
Actually, I can't figure it out myself.
It's just that whenever I see something beautiful,
I think about how I would
love to show Shuichiro.
I'm always reminded of him.
I see.
When I'm reminded of him...
Reminded of him?
There's like a "squeeze", and well,
around my heart I feel a throbbing...
A "squeeze"?
There's like a fuzzy feeling.
All these memories start flowing, of the
satisfaction I feel when I'm by Shuichiro's side,
or the occasional shy smile he shows me...
it just all comes, you know, like...
Like?
Like...
And then the tears come.
I don't understand.
Sorry I'm not able to explain it well.
So what you're saying is when you fall in love
you feel melancholy and you get teary!
Love?
Oh I get it, it's love.
Of course, it's love.
You have no idea.
I read in a magazine that
love comes with distress.
Is there something that is troubling you?
Hmmm... Well maybe...
Yes?
I wouldn't say it's really trouble,
but Shuichiro is always so busy,
that we've never been out on
what you call a "date".
Date?
Oh apparently that's what they call
it when you go somewhere
like an amusement park with the person you like.
A date at the amusement park.
Leave it to me, Kohaku!
Kobato is ready!
I can heal Kohaku's heart by having Shuichiro
take her to an amusement park on a date!
First I'd better do some
research on amusement parks!
So this is an amusement park!
Looks like fun. Huh?
Amusement Park Tickets
Adults 3,000 yen
(Children 1,500 yen)
Amusement Park Tickets
Adults 3,000 yen
(Children 1,500 yen)
Three thousand yen for a ticket?!
Amusement Park Tickets
Adults 3,000 yen
(Children 1,500 yen)
Amusement parks cost money.
But I don't have any money.
What should I do?
Don't ask me. Besides, I don't
think healing Kohaku is...
Ioryogi-san!
First Prize
A Vacation in Hawaii
First prize, a vacation in Hawaii!
Second Prize
A Vacation at a Hot Springs Resort
First prize, a vacation in Hawaii!
Second Prize
A Vacation at a Hot Springs Resort
Second prize, a vacation at a hot springs resort!
Third Prize
Tickets to an Amusement Park
Third prize, tickets to an amusement park!
Spin the box, and the color of the ball that
comes out determines your prize.
All prizes are for two! Step on up,
try your luck at the lottery!
This is amazing! Looks like they're giving
out amusement park tickets!
Line up right here.
Young lady, do you have a lottery ticket?
Huh?
You need a lottery ticket to spin the box.
Oh? I need a lottery ticket before I can
get a ticket to the amusement park?
Lottery ticket...
W-Well, there's no sense in moping over it
forever. Besides, in Kohaku's case...
Lottery ticket.
I guess not too many people drop them.
And here I thought you were all down
in the dumps about this thing!
Now really. How can you even remotely expect a
lottery ticket to be just lying on the street?
Woah!
It's a lottery ticket!
I have a lottery ticket!
I'd like to spin the wheel!
Here!
G-go ahead...
Here goes!
Amusement park tickets...
Congratulations! You are a winner!
What?! I won?!
Is this for real?
Fifth prize!
A stuffed toy alligator! Take good care of it now!
Now that's just one more thing to carry around.
Why didn't you say no?
It's not nice to refuse someone when
they're kindly giving you something.
But...
It has to be an amusement park.
I-I'm sorry!
Fujimoto?
Oh it's you! Pay attention while walking!
You're delivering newspapers?
Yeah.
But Ms. Sayaka told me you
were working at a pizza place.
I work at a pizza place, too.
So many jobs.
What's that?
It's a toy alligator I got from spinning the wheel.
But this alligator just won't do.
Tickets to an amusement park.
Those. They were given to me at work.
Hey.
What are you doing?
May I have these tickets?
Huh? Don't be ridiculous.
Then won't you consider exchanging
these for Mr. Alligator?
No. Why would I want that, anyway?
Please!
It's Kohaku's date at the amusement park!
Here you are.
Please use these on your date with Shuichiro.
Do what you will...
What's with those newspapers?
Oh, they're letting me help deliver newspapers.
You're delivering newspapers so that
you could get those tickets?
Yes! So please.
Thank you very much.
But I really can't take them.
Huh? Why not?
Shuichiro is a very busy man.
It would be impossible.
On the other hand, I wouldn't want to put the
tickets that you especially got for us to waste.
I know. Why don't you go, Kobato?
Huh?
M-Me?!
Yes, with Ioryogi-san.
Huh?
With Ioryogi-san?
Stop imagining it!
No! You must go with Shuichiro!
Otherwise it's meaningless!
But... I really don't think it will be possible.
Besides, I can't be asking favors.
Would that...
...be asking a favor?
When I saw Shuichiro walking with you, Kohaku,
to me he seemed to look very happy.
In the same way that you have
feelings for Shuichiro,
I'm sure that he also sees you
as someone important to him.
I'm sure he wants to go out
on a date with you, too.
Kobato...
Shuichiro.
Huh?
Is it really all right to have those tickets?
Of course it is!
Here! Please!
Shuichiro. You don't mind going with me?
I kind of like ferris wheels.
Hm...
I can't see Kohaku and Shuichiro.
Of course not. Let's go.
Okay...
But I'm sure they're having fun.
I'm sure they are.
Ushagi-san?!
What?
A messenger from Tenkai.
Tenkai? Another acquaintance of yours?
What do you mean, time limit?
By when?
You're saying that the bottle must be
full before four seasons pass?
Huh?
You were listening, right?
Yes. That there's a time limit.
Four seasons, right?
That means that you have
one year to fill the bottle.
And if you don't?
I cannot go to the place of my dreams.
So? Any more in the bottle?
No, the same as before.
Any idea why?
No sir.
Wasn't I able to heal Kohaku's heart?
You need to know that people
who are full of happiness
basically don't need their hearts healed.
Oh, so she wasn't hurt!
What are you so happy about?!
One hundred!
What?! You're giving me one hundred points?
Minus!
Minus one hundred points?
Wrong person! That's enough for
someone who can't get that right.
But, but! It makes me feel
good that she was happy.
You don't have time for that nonsense!
You've got one year!
It's time to get spankin' serious!
Yes sir! Kobato is ready!
Wipe that smirk off of your face!
I don't have a smirk!
I told you, I'm going to get
spankin' serious with you!
Then what does a spankin' face look like?
Like... don't be silly! Can't be done!
No!
Hito wa mina tonde mitai no ni
Juuryoku ni damasareterunda
Dare mo honto wa toberunda yo
Ano ko ga anna ni kanashisou na no wa
Jibun no kage wo
Dokoka ni wasurete kichatta kara kamo
Sore nara
"Arigatou," tte kimi ni ietara
"Arigatou," tte kimi ga waraeba
Ittari kitari ureshiku naru
Kimi ga shiawase ni naru
Shinpai nante iranai yo
Issho ni iru kara
Ureshikuttemo namida ga deru nante
Fushigi da
Next episode
...Firefly Promise.
Fushigi da
Next episode
...Firefly Promise.